Karyna Zubko

Over 2 years of experience in translating complex datasets into clear insights to boost the decision-making process, with a proven track record of enhancing business processes and growth. Let me build a collaboration to achieve new business goals by using data in the right way.



linkedin.com/in/karina-zubko portfolio karunnna2013@gmail.com +38 (066) 28-48-303 Uzhorod, Ukraine

Work Experience

11/2022 - Present

Lisbon, PT - Remote

Business Intelligence Dev & Data Analyst CASAFARI

Accomplishments

Experienced in business product growth, finance, and product KPIs metrics. I used to prepare data reports with comprehensive insights, funnels, and dashboards that help to track required behavior. I used to work with the data pipeline.

SQL, MongoDB, Looker, Tableau, Exel Advnaced, PostHog, Atlassian tools, BigQuery, GA4, Python

09/2021-11/2022

Lisbon, PT - Remote

Market Research Analyst CASAFARI

Accomplishments

Conducting market research based on defined criteria. Extracting, preparing and analysing product data. Analysing market trends and updates. Data extraction that generated >20 000 new leads.

Skills

MySQL, Python (Beautiful Soup), Exel Spreadsheat Automatisation, PowerBI, Git, Statistics

01/2021 - 12/2021

Lisbon, PT - Remote

Data Collection Analyst CASAFARI

Accomplishments

Creating JSON configuration files and Python scripts for data parsing. Providing quality assurance analysis of parsed data. Skills

MySQL, JSON, Jira, Python (Beautiful Soup)

Education

09 / 2021 - 12/2022

Kharkiv, UA - Remote

MA of IS and Tech

Simon Kuznets Kharkiv National University of Economics

Description

- Prepared MS Science Thesis
- Learn analytics approaches, process simulation process automatization
- ETL/ELT (using Python, DAX, R etc.)

09 / 2017 - 06/2021

Kharkiv, UA

BA of Computer Science

Simon Kuznets Kharkiv National University of Economics

Description

- Created Web App as BA Science Thesis
- Participation in student tournaments
- Advance Math, Statistics, Programming languages(C#, C++,Java, R), software & hardware setups

- Project Planning, BA (MS Project, Atlassian)

Strengths

Data Analysis Proficiency

Transformed complex data into understandable reports leading to a 30% increase in effective decision-making.

Business Mindset

Effectively leveraged business requirements to influence data-driven strategies and achieve business goals.

Communication

Excels in presenting complex data in understandable terms, facilitating collaboration across departments.

Skills & Competences

SQL	Looker	Table	au	Superset	Python
MongoDl	B BigQ	uery	Google Analytics		
Business Intelligence			oata S	ETL	
Data Visu	ualisations	A/I	3 Test	ing	

Achievements & Certificates

03 / 202

Google Business Intelligence SpecializationGoogle

12 / 2022

Advanced SQL for Data Scientists
LinkedIn

12 / 2022

Communicating Business Analytics ResultsCoursera

09 / 2022

Developing Data Models with LookMLGoogle Cloud Skills Boost

08 / 2022

Analyzing and Visualizing Data in Looker. Google Cloud Skills Boost

Languages

English - B2

Ukrainian - C2

Interests

Workouts, painting, content-creation, outdoor activities, running, nails-standing, painting, cooking sugar-free deserts